The American Occupation of Iraq. The Inside Story From the Ultimate Insiders.
No End in Sight is a documentary film directed by Charles Ferguson.
Chronological look at the fiasco in Iraq, especially decisions made in the spring of 2003 - and the backgrounds of those making decisions - immediately following the overthrow of Saddam:
no occupation plan, an inadequate team to run the country, insufficient troops to keep order, and three edicts from the White House announced by Bremmer when he took over.
Narrator (voice), played by Campbell Scott.
Gerald Burke, played by Gerald Burke.
Ali Fadhil, played by Ali Fadhil.
Robert Hutchings, played by Robert Hutchings.
Self, played by Seth Moulton.
No End in Sight is a 2007 American documentary film
about the American occupation of Iraq.
The directorial debut of Academy Award-winning documentary filmmaker Charles Ferguson, it premiered on January 22, 2007,
at the Sundance Film Festival and opened in its first two theaters in the United States on July 27, 2007.
By December of that year, it had a theatrical gross of $1.4 million.
The film was nominated for Best Documentary Feature at the 80th Academy Awards.
The film explores themes of the white house, occupying
power, iraq, incompetence, super power.